<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-25T13:02:49+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Regression for IACT</title><subtitle>In this page I will periodically update the status of the project I will be working on.  This is mainly designed for keeping track of my progress and to share it with my mentors and anyone else might be interested in.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">GSoC for OpenAstronomy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/general/2019/04/25/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GSoC for OpenAstronomy" /><published>2019-04-25T12:29:15+02:00</published><updated>2019-04-25T12:29:15+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/general/2019/04/25/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/general/2019/04/25/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;My intent with this site is to allow anyobody who might be interested in my works to follow my progresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve heard about OpenAstronomy and the GSoC thanks to my master thesis supervisor &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rlopezcoto&quot;&gt;rlopezcoto&lt;/a&gt;. I then proposed to work on the project of reconstructing the energy and direction of IACT events with deep learning and to integrates such models in CTLearn, an open-source python library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My experience applying these method comes from the work done in my master thesis where to perform a full reconstruction of data from the currently operating MAGIC telescopes. To do that I started from the calibrated data which I interpolated using scipy in order to make the data computable from the keras deep learning framework. These data was used for solving the &lt;em&gt;regression&lt;/em&gt; problem of &lt;em&gt;energy&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;direction&lt;/em&gt; reconstruction by fitting convolutional neural networks architectures and optimizing them with innovative techniques taken from the recent literature. The full repository with all the code developed for this task is &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mrektor/CNN4MAGIC&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interpolation step is already solved in CTLearn by the DL1-data-handler so I am proposing to implement some of the regression routines using neural networks exploiting multi-task learning (MTL).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">My intent with this site is to allow anyobody who might be interested in my works to follow my progresses.</summary></entry></feed>